

# Chok Eu Tjin | Web Developer

I am an enthusiastic & motivated junior Web Developer who enjoys building things and solving problems. Programming is my passion and I hope to work with like-minded developers. I believe in moving things forward through teamwork and have many experience in collaborating with various individuals/teams. I am interested in both front-end and backend web development opportunities.

22 Sept. 1991

010 8028 8888

Seoul, Korea Malaysia

🔀 eutjin\_72@hotmail.com

https://eutjin-dev.com • https://github.com/eutjin

### Skills

**Programming Languages** Javascript (ES6), HTML, CSS

**Libraries and Frameworks** 

React, NodeJS, Express, MantineUI

**Database** 

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Git, Netlify, Digital Ocean, Figma, Photoshop, Lightroom

#### **Education**

### **Master of Engineering Science**

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR), Malaysia June 2014 - June 2017

### **Research Topic:**

A Novel Algorithm for Optimal Operation and Sizing of Generator-Photovoltaic-Energy Storage System for Minimizing Cost of Energy

Link | PDF

### Research publications:

1.) Novel fuzzy-based control strategy for standalone power systems for minimum cost of electricity in rural areas

Link | PDF

2.) Control Strategies in Energy Storage System for Standalone Power Systems

Link | PDF

3.) Innovative Fuzzy Controller on Island Power Systems with Energy Storage and Renewable for Minimum Fuel Consumption

Link | PDF

## **Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering (Degree)**

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR), Malaysia June 2010 - June 2014

#### **Awards:**

1.) Innovate Malaysia Design Competiton 2014 National Instruments track: Grand Prize

Energy Link: An Interactive Energy Management Platform | URL

2.) Fifth Technopreneurship and Innovation Symposium and Exhibition (TISE) 2013 Young Intellectual category Winner

Dr Energy: a plug-and-play, multifunctional electrical power diagnostic platform | URL

### **Work Experience**

### Technical Support Specialist | Quality Team

GOQUAL Inc. (Korea), May 2018 - Current

I have joined the IoT startup as the 6th member and have held multiple roles ever since. My job roles require me to constantly solve issues and communicate with teams both internal and external to the company.

### Technical Support (Chief Specialist)

- Provide in-depth technical support to the customer service (CS) team
- Design and implement problem solving process flow which enables the CS team to serve end-users in a shorter time period (30% reduction in average communication time with users)
- Provide technical training to employees on product technologies and various product trouble-shooting methods

### Quality Control and Assurance (QC/QA)

- Investigate source of product quality issues/defects and communicate them to manufacturers, so that improvements can be made and future occurrences be prevented
- APP and device firmware testing: Investigate APP/device related issues and provide issue report to software developers
- iOS and AOS APP manual testing/QA before each version update.
- serving 480,000 total registered users, 240,000 Monthly Active Users (MAU), 140,000 Daily Active Users (DAU) with 460,000 total activated devices.

#### **Product Sourcing and Production Management**

- Directly involved in sourcing, developing and launching over 10 different IoT products into the Korean market (currently a market leader in the IoT field)
- Develop systematic product testing and validation methods to ensure the best products are released in short time-to-market period
- Communicate with technical teams from various manufacturers/factories and solve product related issues

#### **Research Intern**

Remotec Technology Ltd. (Hong Kong), July 2017 - January 2018

- · Research project on control algorithm to enable intelligent operation of air conditioners with the aim to reduce energy consumption while maintaining user comfort levels
- proposed algorithms were used by the Research & Development team for product improvement

### **Research Assistant**

Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR), Oct. 2014 - Oct. 2016

- EMS was successfully installed in a university building and energy savings were
- proposed energy control algorithm which was succesfully used in the EMS

### **Projects**

- Gunaesik (React, NodeJS/Express, MongoDB) | URL
- Enerlyzr (React, NodeJS/Express) | URL
- MoviRevue (React, NodeJS/Express, MongoDB) | URL

\*Detailed info available at https://eutjin-dev.com/#projects